<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Humans First on Tracy Bannon</title>
    <link>/tags/humans-first/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Humans First on Tracy Bannon</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 30 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/humans-first/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Reinventing Cybersecurity</title>
      <link>/books/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/books/</guid>
      <description>Books ya gotta check out!! Revinventing Cybersecurity is the first book of its kind written entirely by folks who gender-identify as women and non-binary.
Written by Latha Maripuri, Jasmine Henry, Aubrey Stearn, Carla Sun, Lonye Ford, Dr. Meg Layton, Tracy Bannon, Breanne Boland, Alison Gianotto, Carlota Sage, Lisa Hall, Rin Oliver, Joyous Huggins, Yvie Djieya, Angela Marafino, Coleen Shane, Rachel Harpley, Ashleigh Lee, and Amy Devers.
Reinventing Cybersecurity is the first cybersecurity book written entirely by women and non-binary experts and is a game-changing guidebook for cybersecurity practitioners at all career stages, from analyst to C-Suite.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>About Me Tracy “Trac” Bannon /trās/ Mentor, Speaker, Author, Real Technologist, Tech Evangelist, Change Agent, Human-Focused Software Architect, Ambassador, Engineer I am a real technologist, tech evangelist, and passionate architecxt. My focus is the human side of software architecture. With over 15 years of experince designing, delivering, and continuously improving to deliver value. Some considewr me an accomplished software architect, engineer, and DevSecOps advisor having worked across commercial and government clients.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
