<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Cybersecurity on Tracy Bannon</title>
    <link>/tags/cybersecurity/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Cybersecurity on Tracy Bannon</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 28 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/cybersecurity/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Shift Left Acadermy: Builders and Breakers</title>
      <link>/post/podcasts/buildersandbreakers/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/podcasts/buildersandbreakers/</guid>
      <description>Builders and Breakers Our best way forward towards cyber secure software is teaching builders to think like breakers and breakers to understand builders. Excellent discussion by Tracy Bannon, Casey Ellis, facilitated by Deb Radcliff</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reinventing Cybersecurity</title>
      <link>/books/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/books/</guid>
      <description>Books ya gotta check out!! Revinventing Cybersecurity is the first book of its kind written entirely by folks who gender-identify as women and non-binary.
Written by Latha Maripuri, Jasmine Henry, Aubrey Stearn, Carla Sun, Lonye Ford, Dr. Meg Layton, Tracy Bannon, Breanne Boland, Alison Gianotto, Carlota Sage, Lisa Hall, Rin Oliver, Joyous Huggins, Yvie Djieya, Angela Marafino, Coleen Shane, Rachel Harpley, Ashleigh Lee, and Amy Devers.
Reinventing Cybersecurity is the first cybersecurity book written entirely by women and non-binary experts and is a game-changing guidebook for cybersecurity practitioners at all career stages, from analyst to C-Suite.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Faux Script Kiddie!</title>
      <link>/post/2021/fauxscriptkliddie/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2021/fauxscriptkliddie/</guid>
      <description>A few weeks ago I dusted off my dog-eared copy of ”The Web Application Hacker’s Handbook” by Studdard and Pinto (Yes,I still prefer printed books though I now spring for a second e-version for when I’m traveling.).
I’ve installed the most recent version of Burp Suite community edition and OWASP’s ZAP and decided to freshen up my ethical hacking/cyber-student skills. Of course, I am not probing public sites, but rather, using the ethical learning sites:</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
