<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>DevOps on Tracy Bannon</title>
    <link>/tags/devops/</link>
    <description>Recent content in DevOps on Tracy Bannon</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/devops/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Podcast Series:On the Road to DevHops</title>
      <link>/post/podcasts/ontheroadtodevhops/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/podcasts/ontheroadtodevhops/</guid>
      <description>In this video series, Trac Bannon and Bryan Finster belly up to the bar and have an honest dialog about DevOps, Software Engineering, and delivering value. These two spar, disagree, and even invite few guests when they need new punching bags (just kidding). From being a “SADMF” to Culture to debates on the meaning of Autonomy, the content is relevant and unedited. Trac and Bryan even add an occasional guest to spice up the mix!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Podcast Series:Tech.Strong.Women</title>
      <link>/post/podcasts/techstrongwomen/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/podcasts/techstrongwomen/</guid>
      <description>Tracy Bannon and Charlene O’Hanlon co-host this video series on focused on the challenges and successes that have helped shape women’s collective journey in IT and ways to elevate conversations around equity and parity beyond gender norms.
Guests range from rising starts to CEOs who are all, as I like to say, totally #Badass
View the entire season on Digital Anarchist. Here are the most recent! https://digitalanarchist.com/videos/tech-strong-women
Beyond Gender Norms In this inaugural episode of Tech.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shift Left Acadermy: Builders and Breakers</title>
      <link>/post/podcasts/buildersandbreakers/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/podcasts/buildersandbreakers/</guid>
      <description>Builders and Breakers Our best way forward towards cyber secure software is teaching builders to think like breakers and breakers to understand builders. Excellent discussion by Tracy Bannon, Casey Ellis, facilitated by Deb Radcliff</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DOI: DataOps is not DevOps for a database</title>
      <link>/post/podcasts/dataopsisnotdevops_fordb/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/podcasts/dataopsisnotdevops_fordb/</guid>
      <description>DataOps is not DevOps for a database At the DevOps Online Summint, 2021, Tracy Bannon tries to clear up some things about DataOps. In this conversation, she explains why DataOps is not DevOps for a database! In this converastion, Trac talks with Tom Henricksen about the differences and why folks get confused. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Perseverance, the IRS, and Partnering</title>
      <link>/post/2022/perserverence-the-irs-and-partnering/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2022/perserverence-the-irs-and-partnering/</guid>
      <description>#StraightTalk4Gov and sharing of experience stories is a passion for me. I’ve been thinking about the importance of learn fast/fail fast whether yesterday or earlier. We have a responsibility to share the stories that highlight culture building, organizational change, policy bending, and perseverance
A few years ago I had the opportunity to collaborate with Aaron Francensconi, Amin Qazi, Rupesh Kumar and others at the IRS on adopting agile principles and growing a DevOps practice.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Faux Script Kiddie!</title>
      <link>/post/2021/fauxscriptkliddie/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2021/fauxscriptkliddie/</guid>
      <description>A few weeks ago I dusted off my dog-eared copy of ”The Web Application Hacker’s Handbook” by Studdard and Pinto (Yes,I still prefer printed books though I now spring for a second e-version for when I’m traveling.).
I’ve installed the most recent version of Burp Suite community edition and OWASP’s ZAP and decided to freshen up my ethical hacking/cyber-student skills. Of course, I am not probing public sites, but rather, using the ethical learning sites:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>VSM and DevOps Predictions 2022</title>
      <link>/post/2021/vsm_and_devops_predictions/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2021/vsm_and_devops_predictions/</guid>
      <description>VSM and DevOps Predictions 2022 At the DevOps Online Summint, 2021, Tracy Bannon tries to clear up some things about DataOps. In this conversation, she explains why DataOps is not DevOps for a 2021 has been a breakthrough year for value stream management (VSM). From the inaugural State of VSM report and expansion of the Value Stream Management Consortium to the rise of advanced VSM platforms, value stream management continues to grow as an industry.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
